{
	"questions":[
		{
			"question":"What are the customer benefits from the agile methodology?",
			"level":2,
			"answers":[
				"Customers can make changes without paying exorbitant costs",
				"Customers do not have to be involved throughout the process",
				"Customers can make changes only in the end of the process  ",
				"All of the above"
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":0
		},
		{
			"question":"What are the 3 scrum roles?",
			"level":1,
			"answers":[
				"Product owner, scrum master , development team",
				"Scrum master , QA tester, product owner",
				"Product owner, development team,Team Manager",
				"Development team,Team Manager, QA tester"
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":0
		},
		{
			"question":"Which of the following is true about SRS?",
			"level":3,
			"answers":[
				"Provide a basis for estimating costs and schedules",
				"The SRS requirement document written by the Customer ",
				"SRS Focuses mainly on functional requirement",
				"Requirements cannot change after writing SRS"
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":0
		},
		{
			"question":"SRS stands for?",
			"level":3,
			"answers":[
				"Software requirement standard",
				"Software requirement specification",
				"Software Refinement Specification",
				"Software requirement Subjects"
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":1
		},
		{
			"question":"White box techniques are also called as?",
			"level":3,
			"answers":[
				"error Guessing Technique",
				"Design Based Testing  ",
				"Structural Testing",
				"Experience Based Technique"
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":2
		},
		{
			"question":"Design structure and knowledge of software program is essential in ?",
			"level":2,
			"answers":[
				"Black box testing",
				"Integration testing",
				"White box testing",
				"None of the above"
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":2
		},
		{
			"question":"In Software Maintenance which type of testing is being used?",
			"level":1,
			"answers":[
				"System Testing",
				"Regression Testing",
				"Integration Testing",
				"Unit Testing"
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":1
		},
		{
			"question":"Spotted by users in software maintenance removing errors is known as  ?",
			"level":1,
			"answers":[
				"Adaptive",
				"Preventive ",
				"Perfective",
				"Corrective"
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":3
		},
		{
			"question":"MVC is composed of three components these are  ?",
			"level":1,
			"answers":[
				"Member Vertical Controller",
				"Model variable centered ",
				"Model view controller",
				"Member Vertical Controller"
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":2
		},
		{
			"question":"What Transaction processing systems allow? \t",
			"level":2,
			"answers":[
				"Information in a database to be Internally accessed and modified by a single user.",
				"Information in a database to be remotely accessed and modified by a single user.",
				"Information in a database to be remotely accessed and modified by a number of users.",
				"None of the above."
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":2
		},
		{
			"question":"What are the two peer review methods?\t",
			"level":2,
			"answers":[
				"Inspections and integrations",
				"Inspections and walkthroughs",
				"Verifications and validations ",
				"Walkthroughs and validations ."
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":1
		},
		{
			"question":"What are The major difference between formal reviews and peer review methods\t",
			"level":1,
			"answers":[
				"Responsibility and Punctuality",
				"Participants and responsibility",
				"Participants and objectives ",
				"Objectives and responsibility ."
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":2
		},
		{
			"question":"Which design pattern defines one-to-many dependency among objects?",
			"level":2,
			"answers":[
				"Singleton pattern",
				"Facade Pattern",
				"Observer pattern ",
				"Factory method pattern ."
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":2
		},
		{
			"question":"Which of the following is NOT one of test methods?",
			"level":1,
			"answers":[
				"White box test",
				"JQuery test",
				"JUnit test",
				"Black box test."
			],
			"team":"Sharks",
			"correct_ans":1
		}
	]
}